<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Otter Journal</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Otter Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Second Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/second-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been really thinking about my relationship with Natalie.&#xA;I guess it comes to a couple things:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I don’t really see myself marrying her, my family don’t like her and I think there will be a lot of a cultural clash.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I still feel like I put in more into the relationship than she does. I put my feelings aside so much so she feels better. I contributed 50% more financially. Maybe even close to 80% and now since I’m fasting from sex it’s more of a reason to say that I really don’t get any kind of love from her other than physically. The not sending pictures really hit hard cause I liked looking at them before. I feel like I have a lot of needs unmet.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Trapped. It feels like a chore to be with her. Like I dread driving to see he, or to spend time with her.&#xA;I’ll buy her flowers and write her a note maybe it’ll make her feel better, and she’ll show me more lover. But I think I have to set a certain deadline that if she doesn’t give me specific stuff from here by a certain date than the relationship just isn’t meant to be. Maybe I should just start being super cold and leaver her. No that’s mean. She deserve an explanation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a test post using Hugo and terminal.css 🎉&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
